{"showBridgeTasks":true,"taskHeader":"Concrete Landscape Edging Contractors","categoryPerformanceTest":true,"scrollyPathPageBase":"","providedPostalCode":"","hideAllSemIcons":false,"scrolly_persistedParams":{},"addressId":null,"__cache./api/resource/task/46327/?r_version=1":{"taskOid":46327,"taskName":"Landscape Curbing - Install","taskDescription":"Install or Replace Landscape Curbing","xmTaskDescriptor":"Concrete Landscape Edging Contractors","matchable":false,"profileable":true,"esScore":0.0,"defaultCostGuideTaskId":144,"active":true,"taskKeywords":"Landscape curb mason masonry block","textMessagingName":"Lndscpe Curbing","rolloverLongDesc":null,"rolloverShortDesc":"Permanent concrete edging for landscapes","sectorId":"HS","metaDescription":"Find local contractors to Install or Replace Landscape Curbing.  HomeAdvisor will connect you with prescreened and customer-rated contractors in your area","htmlTitle":"Concrete Landscape Edging \u0026 Curbing \u003ccity\u003e \u003cstatecode\u003e | Concrete Garden Edging","contentDescription":null,"pwcId":16,"acceptGoal":3,"multiZip":false,"preMatchTypeId":5,"bridgeTaskOid":0,"bridgeTaskText":null,"bridgeTaskLinkText":null,"bridgeTaskLinkId":0,"bridgeTaskActive":"N","xmName":"Landscape Curbing Install","redirectToTaskOid":-1,"spDisplayName":"Landscape Curbing - Install","xmHeaderDescriptor":"Describe Your Landscape Project","urlName":"Landscape-Curbing-Install","taskConsiderationId":2,"siteVisible":true,"attributeMatchable":true,"htmlTitleTloc":"\u003cspcount\u003e Best Concrete Landscape Edging Contractors - \u003ccity\u003e \u003cstatecode\u003e | Concrete Curbing","searchKeywords":"Landscape,curb,mason,masonry,block,Curbing,concrete","emcCategoryOid":-12046,"locationDisplayText":"What is the location of your project?","semLocationDisplayText":"To get started, enter the location of your project","commentsPromptText":"Please provide a short description of your project","primaryQuestionSetId":1012,"locationSpecific":false,"commercial":false,"viewFirstParentTask":false},"AdobeFlickerMgmtOn":false,"SCROLLY_FILTER_NON_REQUIRED_33367":false,"headerBranding":{"src":"/images/consumer/cobranding/HA.svg","name":"ha"},"entryPointId":0,"matchingSourceId":2,"scrollyProgressBarTest":false,"isMobile":false,"consumer":{"entityId":0},"affiliateCode":"sm_def_sto","twoPageSubmit":true,"sar":true,"scrolly_customDefaults":["50001_10002","8152_10002","30001_10002","160804_10002","20001_10002","160807_10002","160805_10002","502713_10002","160810_6938","8373_67562","8374_67566"],"entityId":0,"sessionId":"1564368210609pwspr010376737CC5AE756748174EA7F763C984D.pwspr010-1","shouldShowTasks":true,"__cache./api/resource/task/interview/46327/":{"taskOID":46327,"originalTaskOID":46327,"setID":1012,"interviewType":"TASK_INTERVIEW","questions":[{"questionID":7053,"questionDisplayText":"Project Type","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":1,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"What type of landscape curbing project is this?","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":10602,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"New landscape design","answerDisplayText":"New landscape design","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10603,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Replace existing landscape edging","answerDisplayText":"Replace existing landscape edging","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10604,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Replace existing concrete curbing","answerDisplayText":"Replace existing concrete curbing","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":7054,"questionDisplayText":"Linear Feet of Curbing","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":2,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"Approximately how many linear feet of landscape curbing do you plan to install?","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":10606,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Less than 20 ft","answerDisplayText":"Less than 20 ft","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10607,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"20 - 50 ft","answerDisplayText":"20 - 50 ft","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10608,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"51 -100 ft","answerDisplayText":"51 -100 ft","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10609,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"More than 100 ft","answerDisplayText":"More than 100 ft","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":7055,"questionDisplayText":"Desired Border","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":3,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"What curbing or features are you interested in? (Select all that apply)","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":10610,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Mower's Edge","answerDisplayText":"Mower's Edge","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10611,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Angle Edge","answerDisplayText":"Angle Edge","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10612,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"4 x 6 Curb","answerDisplayText":"4 x 6 Curb","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10613,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Colored borders","answerDisplayText":"Colored borders","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10614,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"Lighted borders","answerDisplayText":"Lighted borders","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10615,"answerDisplaySequence":6,"answerText":"Would like recommendation","answerDisplayText":"Would like recommendation","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10616,"answerDisplaySequence":7,"answerText":"Stamped borders (brick, stone, textured, etc.)","answerDisplayText":"Stamped borders (brick, stone, textured, etc.)","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":200130,"questionDisplayText":"Existing Sprinkler System","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":4,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"Do you have an existing sprinkler system?","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":17204,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes, but it will not be affected by the new curbing.","answerDisplayText":"Yes, but it will not be affected by the new curbing.","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":17205,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Yes, it will require modification when installing the new curbing.","answerDisplayText":"Yes, it will require modification when installing the new curbing.","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":90000,"questionDisplayText":"Request Stage","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":1,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Choose the appropriate status for this project:","shortQuestionText":"Project Status:","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":5052,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Ready to Hire","answerDisplayText":"Ready to Hire","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4702,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","answerDisplayText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":80000,"questionDisplayText":"Desired Completion Date","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":2,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"When would you like this request to be completed?","shortQuestionText":"To be completed in:","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":11149,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Timing is flexible","answerDisplayText":"Timing is flexible","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11150,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Within 1 week","answerDisplayText":"Within 1 week","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11151,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"1 - 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"1 - 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11152,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"More than 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"More than 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":7735,"questionDisplayText":"What kind of location is this?","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":3,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"What kind of location is this?","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":true,"answers":[{"answerID":20767,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Home/Residence","answerDisplayText":"Home/Residence","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":20766,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Business","answerDisplayText":"Business","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":501504,"questionDisplayText":"Property Owner","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":4,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Are you the owner or authorized to make property changes? ","shortQuestionText":"Are you the owner or authorized to make property changes? ","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":502713,"questionDisplayText":"Are you interested in financing?","displayToSP":false,"questionDisplaySequence":5,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Are you interested in financing?","shortQuestionText":"Are you interested in financing?","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]}],"questionElements":[{"questionID":7053,"questionDisplayText":"Project Type","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":1,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"What type of landscape curbing project is this?","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":10602,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"New landscape design","answerDisplayText":"New landscape design","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10603,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Replace existing landscape edging","answerDisplayText":"Replace existing landscape edging","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10604,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Replace existing concrete curbing","answerDisplayText":"Replace existing concrete curbing","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":10602,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"New landscape design","answerDisplayText":"New landscape design","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10603,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Replace existing landscape edging","answerDisplayText":"Replace existing landscape edging","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10604,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Replace existing concrete curbing","answerDisplayText":"Replace existing concrete curbing","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":7054,"questionDisplayText":"Linear Feet of Curbing","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":2,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"Approximately how many linear feet of landscape curbing do you plan to install?","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":10606,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Less than 20 ft","answerDisplayText":"Less than 20 ft","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10607,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"20 - 50 ft","answerDisplayText":"20 - 50 ft","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10608,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"51 -100 ft","answerDisplayText":"51 -100 ft","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10609,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"More than 100 ft","answerDisplayText":"More than 100 ft","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":10606,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Less than 20 ft","answerDisplayText":"Less than 20 ft","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10607,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"20 - 50 ft","answerDisplayText":"20 - 50 ft","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10608,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"51 -100 ft","answerDisplayText":"51 -100 ft","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10609,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"More than 100 ft","answerDisplayText":"More than 100 ft","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":7055,"questionDisplayText":"Desired Border","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":3,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"What curbing or features are you interested in? (Select all that apply)","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":10610,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Mower's Edge","answerDisplayText":"Mower's Edge","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10611,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Angle Edge","answerDisplayText":"Angle Edge","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10612,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"4 x 6 Curb","answerDisplayText":"4 x 6 Curb","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10613,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Colored borders","answerDisplayText":"Colored borders","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10614,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"Lighted borders","answerDisplayText":"Lighted borders","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10615,"answerDisplaySequence":6,"answerText":"Would like recommendation","answerDisplayText":"Would like recommendation","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10616,"answerDisplaySequence":7,"answerText":"Stamped borders (brick, stone, textured, etc.)","answerDisplayText":"Stamped borders (brick, stone, textured, etc.)","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":10610,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Mower's Edge","answerDisplayText":"Mower's Edge","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10611,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Angle Edge","answerDisplayText":"Angle Edge","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10612,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"4 x 6 Curb","answerDisplayText":"4 x 6 Curb","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10613,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Colored borders","answerDisplayText":"Colored borders","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10614,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"Lighted borders","answerDisplayText":"Lighted borders","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10615,"answerDisplaySequence":6,"answerText":"Would like recommendation","answerDisplayText":"Would like recommendation","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10616,"answerDisplaySequence":7,"answerText":"Stamped borders (brick, stone, textured, etc.)","answerDisplayText":"Stamped borders (brick, stone, textured, etc.)","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":200130,"questionDisplayText":"Existing Sprinkler System","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":4,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"Do you have an existing sprinkler system?","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":17204,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes, but it will not be affected by the new curbing.","answerDisplayText":"Yes, but it will not be affected by the new curbing.","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":17205,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Yes, it will require modification when installing the new curbing.","answerDisplayText":"Yes, it will require modification when installing the new curbing.","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":17204,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes, but it will not be affected by the new curbing.","answerDisplayText":"Yes, but it will not be affected by the new curbing.","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":17205,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Yes, it will require modification when installing the new curbing.","answerDisplayText":"Yes, it will require modification when installing the new curbing.","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":90000,"questionDisplayText":"Request Stage","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":1,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Choose the appropriate status for this project:","shortQuestionText":"Project Status:","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":5052,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Ready to Hire","answerDisplayText":"Ready to Hire","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4702,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","answerDisplayText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":5052,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Ready to Hire","answerDisplayText":"Ready to Hire","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4702,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","answerDisplayText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":80000,"questionDisplayText":"Desired Completion Date","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":2,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"When would you like this request to be completed?","shortQuestionText":"To be completed in:","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":11149,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Timing is flexible","answerDisplayText":"Timing is flexible","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11150,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Within 1 week","answerDisplayText":"Within 1 week","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11151,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"1 - 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"1 - 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11152,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"More than 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"More than 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":11149,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Timing is flexible","answerDisplayText":"Timing is flexible","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11150,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Within 1 week","answerDisplayText":"Within 1 week","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11151,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"1 - 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"1 - 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11152,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"More than 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"More than 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":7735,"questionDisplayText":"What kind of location is this?","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":3,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"What kind of location is this?","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":true,"answers":[{"answerID":20767,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Home/Residence","answerDisplayText":"Home/Residence","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":20766,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Business","answerDisplayText":"Business","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":20767,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Home/Residence","answerDisplayText":"Home/Residence","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":20766,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Business","answerDisplayText":"Business","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":501504,"questionDisplayText":"Property Owner","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":4,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Are you the owner or authorized to make property changes? ","shortQuestionText":"Are you the owner or authorized to make property changes? ","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":502713,"questionDisplayText":"Are you interested in financing?","displayToSP":false,"questionDisplaySequence":5,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Are you interested in financing?","shortQuestionText":"Are you interested in financing?","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]}]},"KNOWN_USER_SCROLLY_TEST_SITE_33390":"ctrl","semThreeIcons":false,"isCookielessUser":true}